hello everyone my name is pa
tricio lumbe i'm a cloud
engineer i work with
aws cloud and
google cloud and today i would
love to share with you my new
project so the idea behind this
project was to build my
website so i wanted my website
to be
secure fast and shipped
one and also i wanted it to be
scalable and resilient if it
ever needs so
so that's why i chose
google cloud specifically
firebase so firebase it makes a
huge difference in this project
because firebase it serves my
website through a global network
from many servers all over the
world which makes my website
load fast and also it's
scalable and it comes with it's
comes with security built-in
like https and
many other security
tools and all of these in a very
low
cost for infrastructure for
infrastructure for this
project i chose
terraform why because terraform is
a reusable code and simple to
use imagine if i lose tomorrow
all the setup that i applied in
this
project with terraform i can
rebuild my
my infrastructure from scratch
in a question of
minutes so i can review this
project from minute this is a
huge advantage that's why
i chose terraform i can do all
this review in a question of
minute
by running a couple few
comments and for
deployment i chose git up
action so why git up
action because
everything is
automated if i apply any change
in my on my website so the
update is made in a question of
minutes it's also very quick and
it doesn't need any manual setup
with git up action and on top of
that i added monitoring tools
and
alerts with monitoring i can
monitor my website if anything
goes wrong with my website on
cloud i will be notified for a
message
and i'll figure out what is what
happened with my website and
i'll solve this problem before
anyone else doubts so there is
many other tools that i applied
in this project that i would
like to share with you in the
next video and
thank you for watching see you
in the next video